漫威出品
捍卫者联盟
第一季  第七集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     捍卫者联草   苏小黛
翻译     铁拳章鱼X   克里斯
校对     捍奶联盟
时间轴     念念
后期     拳拳和马律师的8T
总监     捍奶联盟
人人影视Pro
人人影视官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方网站下载 : 人人影视Pro
最新海外影视剧下载
人人影视Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在线观看，离线缓存
早      前
你一个人来了
You're alone.
要告诉我为什么吗
Wanna tell me why?
他还没准备好
He's not ready.
真纯会需要马特·默多克
The Chaste needs Matt Murdock.
我试过了  可我说服不了他
I've tried... but I couldn't convince him.
胡扯  你是故意让他脱身的
Bullshit. You let him off the hook.
我派你做过比这难得多的事  艾丽卡
I've sent you to do things a lot harder than this, Elektra.
你说的一切我都照办了
I did everything you said.
我让他对自己最阴暗的冲动屈服了  可他很顽强
I made him give in to his darkest impulses, but he's stubborn.
我无法改变他的心意或秉性
I can't change his mind or who he is.
相反  你让他改变了你
Instead, you let him change who you are.
-并不是这样  -当然是这样
- That's not what happened. - 'Course it is.
你来见我的时候
When have you ever come to me
什么时候夹过尾巴  还给自己找借口
with your tail between your legs, making excuses?
我还以为你不至如此  然而
Thought you were stronger than that, but...
看看你现在这样
here you are,
因为你爱上了他
'cause... you fell in love.
我们就要开战了  没时间想那些
We're going to war. We don't have time for that.
不管你觉得你有什么感觉
For whatever it is you think you're feeling.
他做不到你我做的事
He can't do what you and I do.
暴力是他的本性  但必须达到一个点才会爆发
The violence is part of him, but only to a point.
他永远不会听人命令去杀人
He'll never be able to kill on command.
这可说明他是好人  艾丽
That doesn't make him good, Ellie.
只说明他是弱者
It makes him weak.
不说默多克了
Forget Murdock.
手和会动作很快  有事要发生了  我们得更快
The Hand's moving fast. Something's coming. We gotta move faster.
也许有别的方法打赢你说的这场战争
Maybe there's another way to win this war you talk about...
而不用牺牲这么多人
without so much death?
不管你愿不愿意  艾丽  还会有更多人死
Like it or not, Ellie, more death is coming.
而你我得躲开点
And you and me gotta get out of its way.
我们不能再像这样见面了
We gotta stop meeting like this.
-我什么都不记得了  -我帮你唤醒一下记忆
- I don't remember anything. - Well, let me refresh your memory.
两具尸体  身份未知
Two bodies, unidentified.
一具没了头  一具被刺穿了
One headless, the other impaled.
你要告诉我昨晚发生了什么吗
You wanna tell me what happened last night?
-其他人呢  -那用不着你操心
- Where are the others? - That's none of your business.
但你要是不愿配合  要找你的律师
But if you wanna play it coy and ask to speak to your lawyer,
你该知道他们也收拾了他
you should know that they knocked his ass out, too.
-丹尼·兰德呢  -丹尼·兰德也在场
- Where's Danny Rand? - Danny Rand was there?
-我得走了  -而我得知道答案
- I need to go. - And I need some answers.
我们从简单的开始  那两具尸体是谁
Look, we'll start out easy. Who are the bodies?
谁杀了他们
Who killed them?
是你吗
Was it you?
不是
No.
又不是完全没可能
Well, it's not like it's completely out of the question.
你以前就干过
You've done it before.
我知道你想干什么  没用的
I know what you're trying to do and it's not gonna work.
如果不是你杀的  那是谁
If you didn't kill them, then who did?
你在浪费时间  好吗
You are wasting time, okay?
-会有人受伤的  -已经有人受伤了
- People are going to get hurt. - People are already hurt.
其他人怎么样了
What happened to the others?
他们在走廊那头
They're down the hall.
-他们还好吗  -看起来是的
- Are they okay? - Looks like it.
听着  你得知道我们是一边的
Listen, I need you to realize we are on the same side.
我兑现了我的谈判条件  我保护了你的朋友
Now, I held up my end of the bargain. I protected your friends.
你是时候让我加入了
It's about damn time you dealt me in.
有一个很奇怪的影子组织
There's a weird shadow organization.
我一直在追踪他们
I've been tracking them.
你做得可不怎么样
Not very well.
有多少人
How many were there?
就一个  追杀约翰·雷蒙德的那个
Just one. The same one that came after John Raymond.
什么人能打晕你和卢克·凯奇
What kind of person knocks out you and Luke Cage?
就算我说了  你可能也不会信
I'm not sure you'd believe me even if I told you.
试试看
Try me.
-马特  冷静  -福吉  我们在哪
- Matt. Hold on. - Foggy? Where are we?
哈莱姆分局  私人办公室
Harlem precinct. Private office.
要是描述一下完整画面  你看起来很糟
And if we're painting the whole picture, you look like shit.
-他们拿了你的衣服去采集血样了  -好
- They took your shirt for blood samples. - Right.
克莱尔简单查看了你的伤  骨头没断
Claire gave you a quick look. Nothing's broken.
但警察有很多疑问
But the cops have a lot of questions.
-我当时没穿制服  -我知道  老天开眼
- I wasn't wearing the suit. - I know. There is a God after all.
天  我得走了  他有危险
Oh, God, I need to go. He's in danger.
-谁  -丹尼·兰德  他们抓了他
- Who? - Danny Rand. Uh, they took him.
-那个亿万富翁  -棍叟
- The billionaire? - Stick.
她杀了棍叟
She killed Stick.
对  丹尼  他们抓了丹尼
Yeah, Danny. They took Danny.
现在我得把他从手和会手里救出来
And then now, I have to save him from the Hand.
你现在这状态可救不了任何人
You are in no position to save anybody.
他们还没提起诉讼
They haven't pressed charges,
但他们发现你身边有两具死尸
but they found you with two dead bodies.
我别无选择  他是铁拳
I don't have a choice. He's the Iron Fist.
我可不打算假装我听懂了
I'm not gonna pretend to know what that means.
福吉  干这事的人  抓了兰德的人
Foggy, the person who did this, who, uh, who took Danny...
是艾丽卡
It's Elektra.
-你前女友  -我知道这听起来多荒唐
- Your ex-girlfriend? - I understand how it sounds.
-她死了  -并没有  至少又活了
- She's dead. - She's not. Not anymore.
手和会抓了她  他们对她做了什么
The Hand took her. They did something to her.
不管她是什么  都不是她自己了
Whatever she is, she's not herself.
马特  你得喘口气
Matt, you need to take a breath.
-你这话像疯了  -我不管你信不信
- You sound insane. - I don't care if you believe me.
不管他们要对丹尼·兰德做什么
Whatever they're gonna do with Danny Rand,
对任何人都不会有好处
it is not good for anyone.
-默多克先生  -你是吗  警探
- Mr. Murdock. - Yes. Is that you, Detective?
你醒了
You're up.
你有一个客户在走廊那头吓得快尿裤子了
I've got one of your clients scared shitless across the hallway,
还有一个直接晕了
and the other one passed out,
所以我需要你回答几个问题
so I'm gonna need for you to answer a few questions.
很遗憾
well, unfortunately,
刚才发生的事都受保密协议的保护
whatever happened is protected by attorney-client privilege.
真有趣  不过废话少说
That's cute, but cut the shit.
因为我们都清楚你不仅是个律师
'Cause we both know you're not just a lawyer in all this.
你还有别的身份
You're something more.
目前来说  你是嫌疑人
As of right now, you're a person of interest.
罪行的目击证人
A witness to a crime.
证人
A witness?
你想让我描述下我都听到了什么吗  警探
What, do you want me to describe how it sounded, Detective?
也许你没听到我刚才说"废话少说"
Perhaps you didn't hear me when I said, "Cut the shit."
我听说他们抓走了丹尼·兰德
Now I hear they took Danny Rand.
这种备受关注的人物
A person with that high of a profile?
如果这事怪在你头上  你的生活将步履维艰
If this falls back on you... it's gonna make your life miserable.
听着  我想帮忙
Look, uh... I wanna help.
我不能多说
I can't say much,
不过他现在确实处境不妙
apart from the fact that he is in way over his head.
我们得帮他
And we need to help him.
默多克先生  恕我直言
Mr. Murdock, all due respect,
你得开始考虑怎么拯救自己了
you need to start worrying about helping yourself.
他的脉搏升高了一些
His pulse is up a little.
是好事吗
Is that good?
只要不突然激增  当然是好事
Long as it doesn't spike irregularly, sure.
你觉得那是什么东西
What do you think it was?
某种药物
Some kinda drug.
他们在犯罪现场找到了某种焚香
They found a weird incense at the crime scene.
他的皮肤刀枪不入  其余部分就不是了
His skin's what's bulletproof. The rest of him is not.
你觉得丹尼会活下来吗
You think Danny would have survived it?
我不知道  科琳
I don't know, Colleen.
好吧  我们得弄清发生了什么
Okay, we need to find out what happened.
他还要昏迷多久
How long until he wakes up?
可能一个小时  也可能一周
Could be an hour. Could be a week.
我知道
I know.
天啊  我们怎么会沦落到这
God, how the hell did we get here?
和他们一起
With them?
我竭尽所能避开有超能力的人
I did everything I could to avoid people with abilities.
辞了工作
Quit my job.
搬到了上城区
Moved my ass uptown.
-结果怎么样  -你说呢
- And how'd that work out? - You tell me.
我这跟班当得还行吧
Is sidekick a good look on me?
他们在进行一场正义的战斗  你也是
They are fighting a good fight. You're doing it, too.
和他们不同
Not like them.
甚至和杰西卡不同
And even Jessica.
注定要有逃离火场的人
There are people who run from the fire,
也有义无反顾冲进去的人
and there are people who run into it.
这些傻子
Dumb people.
你说过我是团队的基础  对吗
Okay, you said I was the foundation, right?
看看镜中的自己
Look in the mirror.
即便在遇到卢克之前
Even before you met Luke,
你也不是那种会袖手旁观的人
you weren't the type who could just... stand by and watch.
对吗
Were you?
克莱尔
Claire?
-我在哪  -你在警局  感觉怎么样
- Where am I? - You're in the precinct. How do you feel?
丹尼怎么了
What happened to Danny?
他还活着吗
Is he alive?
这不是我们的行事方式
This is not how we do business.
现在是了
It is now.
不管你是不是黑空  我们现在是三对一
Black Sky or not, there are three of us and one of you.
这是在挑衅吗
Is that a challenge?
我们会竭尽所能维护我们的组织
We will do what is needed to preserve our organization.
而这不是首选方案
This is not our first coup.
没了圣物  这就是首选方案
It is your first without the substance.
你愿意以此冒险吗
Is that a gamble you're willing to take?
手和会是个全球性组织
The Hand is a global organization.
这些年来  亚历山德拉一直致力于
For years, Alexandra fostered relationships
发展与犯罪头目乃至企业合伙人的联系
with everything from crime lords to corporate partners.
企业合伙人
Corporate partners?
我们怎么跟他们解释她的死
How do we explain her death to them?
没有解释的必要
There's no need for explanations.
什么
What?
这些联系让我们能秘密地行动
These relationships grant us invisibility in our operations.
我们的秘密协定  我们的政治派系
Our back-room accords. Our political affiliations.
这给了我们力量
This gives us power.
这不是力量
This isn't power.
藏身地下  畏首畏尾
Living underground. In hiding.
你对力量一无所知
You know nothing of power.
在亚历山德拉把你救活前  你甚至都不存在
You didn't exist until Alexandra gave you life.
是吗
Didn't I?
问题不是你做了什么  而是你的行事方法
It's not what you did, it's how you did it.
手和会之所以能长久存在  是因为我们
The Hand has survived this long because we,
能精明行事
above all else, have been astute.
也许这话你没想到
Well, this may come as a bit of a shock,
不过我不在乎手和会
but I don't care about the Hand.
我在乎的是圣物
I care about the substance.
因为从今天起  没什么能够阻止我
Because from now on, nothing will stand in my way.
连死亡也不能
Not even death.
-你们没事吧  -我死不了
- You guys okay? - I'll live.
我猜你们谁都没偷偷捎瓶酒进来吧
I don't suppose either of you snuck a flask in here.
我们要怎么脱身
How are we gonna get out of this?
我还想问你这个问题呢
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
你们三个想坐下吗
Three of you wanna sit?
请自便
Suit yourself.
我们没能确定
We've had no luck identifying
在仓库一并发现的那些尸体的身份
the bodies we found in the warehouse with you.
今天你们两个有不少犯罪记录
And though you two have colorful histories,
我已经提醒纽约警方
I have reminded the NYPD
-我们没有证据  -暂时没有
- we have no evidence... - Yet.
能表明  你们负有责任
...to suggest that you were responsible.
我信任奈特警探
Now, I trust Detective Knight,
她说  虽然你们都严守口风
and she says that, although you're being tight-lipped,
最佳策略
the best way to proceed
是把你们当做证人  而不是嫌犯
is to treat you as witnesses and not suspects.
你们掌握了能填补空白的信息  我们需要它
You have information that can fill in the gaps. We need it.
我们的特遣队
Our task force
追踪一个神秘犯罪组织数月了
has been tracking a mysterious crime syndicate for months.
他们行动快  会掩盖行踪
They move fast and cover their tracks
伤了不少无辜者
and often with the blood of innocent people.
-人们有危险  -警监  我的委托人都累坏了
- People are in danger. - Captain, my clients are exhausted
而且情绪激动
and under emotional distress.
我相信你能理解他们多需要回家
I'm sure you understand they need to go home.
我觉得你不理解
And, see, I'm not sure you understand
现在情况多严重
the severity of the situation.
所有接触过这些混蛋的人  都死了
Everyone who's come in contact with these assholes turns up dead.
要么你们帮我们
Now, either you help us
要么我就去腾出几间牢房
or I start clearing out a couple of jail cells.
他们自称手和会
They call themselves the Hand.
他们是真实存在的  是一帮杀人犯
They're real. They're murderers.
他们抓走了丹尼·兰德
And they took Danny Rand.
-他们要他做什么  -我不知道
- But what do they want with him? - I don't know.
他们找他挺久了
They've been after him for a while now.
谁知道他们接下来会做什么
Who knows what they'll do next.
罪犯觉得自己获胜时  会大意
Look, when criminals feel like they're winning, they get sloppy.
这对我们可能是好事
This could be good for us.
不  这些罪犯不会
No, not these criminals.
他们不会大意  只会更加危险
They don't get sloppy. They just get more dangerous.
必须由我们来  我们能解决这事
It has to be us. We can take care of this.
"我们"  才没什么"我们"
"We"? There is no "we."
义警没有管辖权  纽约警局才有
Vigilantes don't have jurisdiction. The NYPD does.
卢克  你不需要保护我们
Luke, you don't need to protect us.
告诉我们去哪找到手和会  让我们接手
Tell us where to find the Hand. We can take it from there.
我不能
I can't.
那好吧
Well, that's it. Okay.
谁去打给托尔地检官  我受够了这么绕来绕去
Someone call DA Tower. I'm tired of doing this the hard way.
这些人不能对我们指手画脚  我们才是法律
These people don't tell us what to do. We are the law here.
还是纽约市已经完全疯了
Or has New York gone completely insane?
警监  你打电话之前
Captain, before you make any calls,
我想跟我的委托人商量一下
I'd like to sidebar with my clients.
你可以那么做
Oh, you can do that...
但我要先以妨碍司法公正罪扣押他们  还有你
after I book them for obstruction. And you.
就私下谈一句
Just a word. In private.
我想跟他们解释
I would like to explain to them
要如何能配合你立案
how best to cooperate in building your case.
希望他们听你的
Well, I hope they like what you have to say.
否则  我警告你
Otherwise, and I warn you,
我会让你跟两个超能人士关在一起
I'm putting you in a room with two super-powered people.
据我所知  他们还享有合法权益
Last I heard, they still have legal rights.
-知道吗  小子  -警监
- You know what, son... - Captain...
让他们谈吧
I think we should let them.
相信我
Just trust me.
好吧  但别让我后悔
Okay. But don't make me regret this.
谢谢  警监
Thank you, Captain.
警探  我可以跟默多克先生谈谈吗
Detective... would you mind if I grab Mr. Murdock for a moment?
一会儿就好
I'll just be a minute.
-好吧  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thank you.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我可以稍后再解释吗
You mind if I explain later?
看上去不妙啊
Well, it looks pretty bad.
要不了多久
It's only a matter of time
他们就会开始搞明白联系了
before they start to put things together.
我知道
Yeah, I know, I know.
天呐
God.
我不懂  你努力付出了那么多
I don't understand. After everything you've worked for?
你终于开始重建你的生活了
You were finally rebuilding your life.
凯伦
Karen...
这就是我的生活
this is my life.
我得去了
I have to go.
丹尼为这场仗准备了一辈子
Danny's prepared his whole life for this fight.
他是铁拳
He's the Iron Fist.
而且他见人就说
And he will tell that to anyone who will listen.
我了解他
I know him.
内心深处
Deep down inside...
他还是那个寻找家人的孩子
he is still just a kid looking for his family.
在我
With me...
在他们那儿
and with them...
他几乎找到了
almost had it.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
谈什么
About?
我本来是想让你帮助一个家庭
Look, I brought you in to help one family.
但这事要失控了
But this shit is getting out of hand.
我知道  已经失控了
I know. It's already out of hand.
我知道你是想做好事
I know you're trying to do good,
但做英雄和做殉道者是有区别的
but there is a difference between being a hero and a martyr.
你觉得那是我让大家冒险的原因吗
You think that's why I'm putting everyone at risk,
因为我的骄傲
because of my pride?
我不知道该怎么想  或许你想做回警察
I don't know what to think. Maybe you wanna be a cop again.
事实上  我看不懂你的计划了
The truth is, I've lost sight of your plan.
-没有计划  -我看出来了
- There is no plan. - I can tell.
-卢克  我是你的朋友  -我知道  米丝蒂
- Look, Luke, I am your friend. - I know, Misty.
所以我才想保护你
That's why I'm trying to protect you.
让我保护你吧  求你
Let me. Please.
我不信任她
I don't trust her.
我们要不要阻止她
What if we stop her...
免得她毁掉了我们所做的一切
before she undoes everything we've done?
铁拳被带去门那里了
The Iron Fist is being led to the door.
我们从未这么接近过
We're closer than we've ever been.
她不是我们的一员
She is not one of us.
那无所谓
It does not matter.
她有能力给我们带来新的开始
She has the ability to bring us a new beginning.
之后  一切都有可能
And after that, anything can happen.
我们在这下面做什么
What are we doing down here?
那要看你的了
That depends on you.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我们没多少时间了
We don't have a lot of time.
如果他们要起诉
If they're pressing charges,
我们需要个你之外的律师
we want a lawyer who isn't you.
-那不是我们在这儿的原因  -没错
- That's not why we're here. - You're right.
我们在这儿是因为你的前任差点把我们都杀了
We're here because your ex almost killed every one of us.
是啊  她是带走了丹尼还是杀了他
Yeah, did she take Danny or did she kill Danny?
我不知道  但如果棍叟说的是真的
I don't know. But if what Stick said is true,
他们没留下他的尸体
and they didn't leave his body behind,
我们得相信他们需要他活着
we have to believe they need him alive.
说起来  我觉得她救了他
If anything, I think she saved him.
你们冲进来时  那老头正打算杀了他呢
When you burst in, the old man was trying to slice him open.
他肯定是知道手和会打算拿铁拳
Well, he must've known what the Hand was planning on
做什么
doing with the Iron Fist.
-是什么  -我们还是不知道
- Which is what? - We still don't know.
他们带丹尼去哪了
Where did they take Danny?
中城圈最有可能
Midland Circle makes the most sense.
你们从建筑师那里找到了什么
What did you get from the architect?
他打算炸掉大楼
He was planning on blowing up the building.
让它塌入下面的大洞里
Collapsing it straight down into the hole.
-他们还在挖吗  -不  挖掘已停止
- They're still digging? - No. Digging stopped,
但有个什么建筑  穹顶形的...
but there's some structure, some dome-shaped thing...
我们在钢琴里发现了蓝图
We found blueprints inside the piano.
-什么  -别问
- The what? - Don't ask.
如果他们认为丹尼是钥匙
If they think Danny's a key,
那么他能打开的东西  或许在那个建筑里
maybe whatever it is he unlocks is in that structure.
天呐  这真是最蠢...
Oh, my God, this is the dumbest...
问题是  我们该怎么办
The question is, what are we gonna do about it?
我刚出狱
I mean, I just got out of jail.
他们不知道你的身份  马特
They don't know who you are, Matt.
-天呐  给我们点时间  -不是警察
- Jesus! Give us a minute! - It's not the cops.
抱歉  能跟你说句话吗
Sorry. Can I borrow you?
-现在没空  -就现在
- Not right now. - Yes, right now.
马上回来
Just give me a minute.
-马特  你得听我说  -能不能快点
- Matt, I need you to hear me out. - Can you please make this fast?
我觉得你不懂你现在的情况多严重
I don't think you understand the gravity of your current situation.
你的现实生活  和另一个生活
Your real life and your other life
现在是两辆有相撞危险的列车
are two trains dangerously close to colliding right now.
我很清楚
I am well aware.
你听到那警察的话了吗
Did you hear what that cop said?
如果你遭到了调查  你会失去一切
If you're ever investigated, you lose everything.
他们会重开每件案子
They'd reopen every case.
事实上  我也会受拖累
Matter of fact, I come with you.
我们都被取消律师资格
We both get disbarred.
对不起  我现在没这个时间
I'm sorry. I don't have time for this now.
整个城市都有危险
The entire city is in danger.
我知道  我也没蠢到认为我能阻止你
I know. And I'm not dumb enough to think I can try and stop you.
我来
I'm here
是想帮你分开你的两个生活
because I'm trying to help you keep your two lives separate.
免得他们把你跟刀枪不入先生
So they don't lump you in with Mr. Bulletproof
和超级琼·杰特一起关起来
and Super Joan Jett in there.
-你懂吗  -我懂
- You understand? - Yeah, I do.
那好
Okay, good.
因为这栋楼里的人永远
'Cause the people in this building need to always,
只能当你是个律师
and only, see you as a lawyer.
我知道
I know.
这是什么
What is this?
我还有你家的钥匙
I still have a key to your place,
我给你带了换洗衣服
so I brought you a change of clothes.
-好  谢谢  -不客气
- Okay, thank you. - Anytime.
-那好  -家人就是干这个的嘛
- All right. - That's what family's for.
杰西和我谈了  不管需要什么
Look, Jess and I have been talking, and no matter what it takes...
不管我们要跟这些警察说什么
no matter what we have to tell these cops,
我们必须得去中城圈
we gotta get to Midland Circle.
好  只要我们都达成一致
Okay. So long as we're on the same page.
以下是我的正式法律建议
Here's my official legal advice.
你得从那三个人口中撬出点什么来
You need to get something out of those three.
卢克和杰西卡觉得他们在保护我们
Luke and Jessica think they're protecting us.
那个律师  天知道他是怎么回事
And the lawyer, God knows what his play is.
我不在乎
I don't care.
这种案子能决定事业
This is the kinda case that makes or breaks a career.
而且我不是指自己
And I'm not talking about mine.
你查到并阻止这个阻止  不管他们是谁
Now, you track down and stop this organization, whoever they are,
上头会挤破头
and brass will be knocking each other over
来跟你握手
trying to shake your hand.
但如果你不能破案
But you don't break this case,
他们也会记住的
they'll remember that, too.
该死
Shit!
你认得那语言吗
Do you recognize that language?
你就是为此带我下来
That's why you dragged me down here?
做翻译
To be a translator?
上面说什么
What does it say?
我见过这种语言  但很多我还没学
I've seen this language before, but there's a lot I didn't learn.
他们有好多没告诉我
A lot they didn't tell me.
而且  就算我认得
Besides, even if I could read it...
我也不知道这是什么
I have no idea what this is.
幸好  我知道
Well, lucky for us, I do.
多年前  有个你这样的人用他的能力封印了这里
Years ago, someone like you used their abilities to seal this.
-你怎么知道  -亚历山德拉说话  我听了
- How do you know? - Alexandra talked. I listened.
他的行为  确保了只有一样东西能打开它
In doing so, they guaranteed that only one thing could open it.
另一个铁拳
Another Iron Fist.
门后  是手和会真正的力量
Behind that door is the true power of the Hand.
你指望我为你打开吗
And you expect me to open it for you?
我向师父发誓
I swore an oath to my masters
会保护昆仑  毁掉手和会
to protect K'un- Lun and destroy the Hand.
我也有过主人
I also had masters.
但我现在自由了  你也可以
But I'm free now. And you can be as well.
派三队人马在10个街区范围内搜索
I want three units scouring a ten-block radius.
他们不可能跑远  警探
They can't be far. And, Detective...
长官  我以为卢克没这么蠢  我以为...
Sir, I thought Luke was smarter than this. I thought...
如果你想自保
If you want a chance to save yourself here,
你得重新考虑你究竟多了解这些义警
you need to reconsider how well you know these vigilantes.
明白了吗
That clear?
找到他们
Find them.
该死
Shit.
他们发了我们的全境通告
They got an APB out on us.
他们以为你们绑架了我
They think you guys kidnapped me.
太好了
Great.
我们还得走20个街区
We're still 20 blocks away.
我们得离开大道
We need to stay off the streets.
坐出租车吗
Should we take a cab?
-他们留下了我的钱包  -我的也是
- They kept my wallet. - Yeah, me, too.
该死
Shit.
我们不管做什么  都得赶快行动
Whatever we do, we need to do it fast.
地铁卡
这一周太漫长了
It's been a long week.
福吉
Foggy!
-他们走了  -是啊
- They're gone! - I know.
他们以为卢克和杰西卡绑走了马特
They think Luke and Jessica took Matt?
-不可能吧  -你觉得呢
- That can't be true, right? - What do you think?
走吧
Well, come on.
我觉得马特从未做过他不想做的事
I think Matt's never done a damn thing he didn't want to.
-是啊  -我不懂
- Yeah. - I don't get it. I don't get it.
他就要开始新生活了  为什么又要冒险
He was so close to moving on. Why would he risk it again?
因为他必须  因为这事很大
Because he has to. Because this thing is huge.
因为  我叫他去的
And because... I told him to.
-你什么  -别担心  他不是作为马特去的
- You did what? - Don't worry. He didn't go as Matt.
你给了他紧身衣
You gave him the suit?
我并不是想为他打开门
I wasn't trying to open the door for him.
而是给他个机会永远关上门
I was giving him a chance to close it. For good.
不管这事是怎么回事  等它结束了
Look, whatever this is, when it's done,
马特应该就会回归
I think we'll get Matt back.
整个警局都处于警戒状态
Whole precinct's on alert now
很快  全城的警察都会开始追捕他们
and pretty soon every cop in the city is gonna be on the hunt.
如果你知道他去哪了  你得告诉我
So if you know where he's going, you need to tell me.
我不知道
I don't know.
但我确定不管卢克去了哪  他必须去那里
But I'm pretty sure wherever Luke is, it's where he needs to be.
你想再等几年再见到他吗
Are you ready to wait a couple years before you can see him again?
因为你和我都清楚
'Cause you know and I both know
他几乎不可能
it's gonna be damn near impossible
不承担任何后果
for him to get away with this shit.
你知道真北是什么吗
You know what his true north is?
做正确的事  不顾后果
Doing the right thing, no matter the consequence.
就我看来  他终于找到自己在这世上的位置了
Far as I can tell, he's finally finding his place in the world.
听着  我只是不希望他失去一切
Look, I just don't want to see him lose everything
他努力争取来的东西
that he's worked hard for.
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help.
哈莱姆不能失去他
Harlem can't afford to lose him.
他出狱后的第一天
You know, on his first day out of lockup,
你带他去散步
you took him on a walk...
告诉他  他能够改变这个城市
and told him that he was capable of turning this city around.
拯救别人
Of saving somebody.
那正是他现在在做的
That's exactly what he's trying to do right now.
或许给你和纽约警局造成了不便
It may not be convenient for you or the NYPD.
对于我更是如此
It's really not convenient for me.
但我们很幸运他是那种
But we're damn lucky he's the kind of man
不许任何事阻拦他的人
that doesn't let anything stand in his way.
等等  那个拿武士刀的小妞呢
Wait a minute, where's the chick with the sword?
该死
Oh, shit.
我们还有时间喝一杯吗  或者三杯
We have time to grab a drink? Or three?
-犹豫了  -不是
- Having second thoughts? - No.
或许吧  你呢
Maybe. You?
没有
No.
或许吧
Maybe.
-我们怎么进去  -后门  停车场
- So how do we get in? - Back entrance. Parking garage.
我几天前来找丹尼  就那么进去的
I came looking for Danny a couple days ago. That's how I got in.
几天前  天呐  那感觉像是三周前了
A couple days? God, that feels like three weeks ago.
可不是呢
Yeah, tell me about it.
又来了
There it is again.
好了
All right.
-怎么了  -有别人
- What's wrong? - We're not alone.
迈克尔杰克逊舞步重现
MJ deep cut.
-几个  -三个  有武器
- How many? - Three. Armed.
-就三个吗  -不是一般人
- Just three? - Not just any three.
去大堂  中城圈
-那是唯一进去的路吗  -很不幸  是的
- Is that the only way in? - Unfortunately.
我们来找丹尼·兰德
We're here for Danny Rand.
铁拳是我们的
The Iron Fist belongs to us.
没有他  我们不会走的
Well, we're not leaving here without him.
那你们就别想走了
Then I guess you're not leaving.
我们不用非要战斗
We don't have to fight.
手和会只会战斗
Fighting is all the Hand knows.
我不是手和会
I'm not the Hand.
我们被利用了  我们都是
We've been used. Both of us.
我们被养大去打别人的仗
We've been raised to fight someone else's war.
但你和我  我们是一样的
But you and I, we're the same.
我们只想决定自己的未来
All we want to decide is our own futures.
你听上去像你的主子  亚历山德拉
You sound like your master, Alexandra.
但你们都不知道我想要什么
But neither of you know what I want.
亚历山德拉死了
Alexandra's dead.
我杀了她
I killed her.
这是我想要的
That's what I wanted.
那你呢  你想要的不止昆仑吧
And you? You wanted more than K'un-Lun.
所以你弃之而去了  对不对
That's why you abandoned it, isn't it?
他们告诉了我你的事  你的挣扎
They told me all about you. About your struggle.
但是有什么意义
But what was it for?
你还是一个人来面对
You're still at this alone.
尤其是你知道了是你那些宝贝长老
Especially since you know that your precious elders
故意选择对你隐瞒真相
chose to keep you in the dark.
和我的遭遇一样
Just like mine did.
你我唯一的不同就是我抓住了我的命运
The only difference between us is that I took my destiny.
而你却在逃避命运
You ran away from yours.
也许你说得对
Maybe you're right.
也许我确实是在逃避
Maybe I did run.
也许这世界上确实有许多事物
Maybe there were things in this world
我还没有准备好要面对
that I wasn't ready to confront.
但是你
But you...
并不是其中之一
you are not one of them.
警告你  我比我看起来强多了
I should warn you, I'm stronger than I look.
什么
What the...
今天你别想
Not today.
点燃  马上
Light! Now!
大家还好吗
Everyone okay?
早就不好了
Okay is long gone.
你应该待在分局
You should be at the precinct.
不用客气
You're welcome.
我知道你想要什么  但你得不到的
I know what you want, but you're not gonna get it.
因为和你不同  我的师父教会了我忠诚
Because unlike you, my master taught me loyalty.
所以你仍然被你的师父束缚着
that's why you're still chained to your master.
你在这里一样会失败  就像在昆仑一样
You're gonna fail here, just as you failed K'un-Lun.
你真该听听他们被我杀的时候是怎么惨叫的
You should've heard the way they screamed when I killed them.
他们逃走了  马特
They gone, Matt?
是  暂时吧
Yeah, for now.
袋子里是什么
What's in the bag?
我来是为了救丹尼  也为了不再有人受伤害
I'm here to save Danny and make sure no one gets hurt ever again.
-这跟我的问题有什么关系  -我们得走了
- How does that answer my question? - We have to go.
袋子里到底是什么
What's in the bag?
她说得对
She's right.
站住
Hold it.
-克莱尔  -这里发生什么了
- Claire? - What happened here?
没时间解释了
No time to explain.
-没时间才怪  -拜托了
- Like hell there isn't. - Please.
给你们一分钟解释
You got a minute
再晚纽约全部警力就都赶到了
before the full force of the NYPD is here.
所以我需要你们干脆回答
So I need you to answer this fast.
你们需要我拖多长时间
How long you want me to stall 'em?
肯定不是好事
That can't be good.
是啊
Nope.
米切尔·埃里森
是  我是凯伦  我们这也没电了
Yeah, it's Karen. Yeah, our lights, too.
继续行动
Keep moving.
警察来了
Cops coming.
还真是想不到
You have no idea.
不许动
Freeze!
可恶
Shit.
-不要开火  -收到
- Hold your fire. - Copy that.
奈特  你去哪了
Knight, where have you been?
我怀疑他们可能来这了  警监  就下来了
I had a feeling they were here, Captain, so I came down.
-那他们在吗  -在
- Well, are they? - Yeah.
但是我刚到这  就没电了  他们也不见了
But by the time I got here, lights went out, they were gone.
警监  楼梯井里有动静
Hey, Cap! We got movement in the stairwell.
可恶
Shit.
-丹尼在哪  -是啊  丹尼在哪
- Where's Danny? - Yeah, where is Danny?
地下还有建筑  他肯定就在下面
There's a structure underground. He's gotta be there.
-我们怎么下去  -正在想办法
- How do we get to it? - Figuring that out.
我不喜欢这里  完全不喜欢
Hey, I don't like it here. Not at all.
说晚了
Too late.
那边有部电梯  能下到很深的地方
There's an elevator this way. It goes deep.
-你认为他在下面  -去看看吧
- Think he's down there? - Let's find out.
还有件事
Just one more thing.
那是什么
What is that?
炸药
不会吧
This is not happening.
我们找到丹尼就把他救出来
We grab Danny and we get him out,
但如果不毁灭手和会
but if we don't end the Hand...
他们早晚会追杀过来
sooner or later, they'll come after us.
-我的天啊  -怎么会这样
- Oh, my God. - This is not happening.
那个设计师是你调查的吧
The architect, he was your guy, right?
少把这破事怪我头上
Don't put this shit on me.
不是  他在计划怎么把这栋楼炸掉
No. He had this plan on how to take this thing out.
我的确想救丹尼  但可不是这么救的
Okay, I wanna save Danny, too, but not like this.
我们会被指控妨害公务  还有境内恐怖袭击
They'll have us on obstruction of justice and domestic terrorism.
这不只关于丹尼  更关乎整个纽约城
This isn't just about Danny. It's about New York.
你了解这些人  克莱尔  他们凶狠无情
You know these people, Claire. They're relentless.
但是炸了这栋大楼也不能保证
There's no guarantee that exploding this building
彻底毁掉他们的组织
ends their organization.
这样能捣毁他们的领导层  斩断他们的首脑
It kills their leaders and cuts the head off the snake.
我们是来救命的  不是来夺命的
Hey, we're here to save lives, not take them.
-这些人并非真正活着  -而且这楼是空的
- These people aren't really alive. - Plus the building is empty.
再没有其他人了  只有我们和他们
There's no one else here. It's us and them.
你接受这事吗
You're okay with this?
当然不  可是  她说得对
I mean, no, but... she's right.
而且设计师早就知道
And the architect knew it.
终结这一切的唯一方法
The only way to end this,
想拯救这座城市免遭毁灭
to save the city from whatever's coming,
就只能炸毁大楼
is to bring this building down.
所以如果没有反对意见的话
So unless there are any objections...
那我们就这么办了
then that's exactly what we're gonna do.